{
    "id": "e4e3a7d2efac4ac6bdce3e65f5014291",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She accused me ………………. stealing her watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dac5a269c63d4f7ebc0dea827765da7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am afraid ………………… cockroaches.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4276d762182744b79856beff6762ed5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She left the firm because she could not agree ………………. their policies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "991a52ffd9f24623b234d050d0b96d79"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you angry ………………. me?",
            "description": "Both 'at' and 'with' are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8303299282d64bc0a3bbf2d1956ee2b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is anxious ……………….. an end to this misunderstanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e203ceca65d437199634ab6fe59c683"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize …………………. disturbing him.",
            "description": "We apologize for something.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68a7d6aa2b8c4940a8f6d2042ac3cef8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize ………………. your colleagues.",
            "description": "We apologize to somebody for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dde2fc6cac1e4890b499ac2a8b7c3cc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrived ………………. Budapest in the evening.",
            "description": "Both 'at' and 'in' are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31726e5d911a4b069b90aeecb67ea56a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not very good ……………… badminton.",
            "description": "We use good at, bad at, clever at etc.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "12093bf450254ad8914e9d1a06cfac3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe ……………… life after death?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "44a4c22bf1224504a017895d36afdee5"
        }
    ]
}